Right.
So this code is already, I will be providing this
to you in about the video.
Download that and uh, put that in the folder.
Mission D-H-H-O-F.
Now we'll go back to a WS console
and this time, see the notebook was
for iterative code development.
Okay? When it comes to really running the code
as a data pipeline job, you need to use this script data.
So we'll click on that and it's a Pi Spark job.
So we'll leave the engine as Spark itself
and click on Create Script.
We have a boilerplate code here.
We'll delete this code and we'll go
to our visual studio code.
Control a copy, right click copy, go back to glue,
right click paste.
It's all pasted here.
Now the next thing, give the job a name.
So we'll go down to our VS code,
right click on the file name rename.
We can now copy do control C,
or you can also come here and do copy here.
Go back to the glue, click here,
remove the untitled Job characters.
Right Click and paste. There you go.
The, and then finally enter on your keyboard.
This will show the job details here.
Now you're gonna go and click on this.
Now, now we need to provide the role name, okay?
There's a role name that your team would've
provided, which is Mission, D-H-H-O-F, inclusive role.
And then we'll scroll down.
Now we don't need 10 workers, right?
We just need minimum of two workers. That's enough for us.
We'll change this to two.
Scroll down, everything else looks good.
So we'll go to this button called a save,
and then click on save.
That will create the job. So it's all done.
We can now run the job by clicking on the run button.
That's pretty much, so it has successfully started the job.
And it says to navigate run details.
We can click on the run details now,
and it takes us to this particular menu here.
Let we zoom out a bit.
It is running right now, and we can refresh it right here.
We just refresh it still running. We scroll down a bit.
We can click on the output log site here,
and, uh, it'll take us to the CloudWatch service
and we can just scroll down and click on this log stream.
This will show us that the job is running here, in fact,
but this'll take a few minutes and, uh, then you should see
the run status has finished, and you can go back to your S3
and then you can take a look there.
You should see the data for 2094
and 2025 for all the months and all the days.
So that's it for this job.
And, uh, we'll see what we need to do
to load the data from the curated to aggregated layer asset.